Tams-Witmark Collection
Music Division, Library of Congress
- Music (Box 1-829)
  - De Koven, Reginald, 1859-1920
    - Selections from: The Man in the moon; The Jersey lily; [Mineographed lyrics]; Red feather; Tzigane, Manuscript piano-vocal score; sketches (Box 789)
    - Solo piano selections: In minor mode: preludes for pianoforte (nos. 11, 12 only); Poet's dream: waltzes for pianoforte, Manuscript piano score (Box 782)
    - Songs (non-theatrical): Berceuse; Elegie: sweet my love is dead; I'd like to go to dreamland ev'ry day; Melanie: menuet intermezzo; Down the Bayou -- A Creole serenade, Manuscript piano-vocal score; sketches (Box 782)
    - Miscellaneous materials: In springtime; Nothing doing; Sons of Mars; Tweedle Dum and Tweedle Dee; A Hundred years from now, Manuscript piano-vocal score (Box 790)
  - Delibes, Léo, 1836-1891
    - [Coppélia]
      - Coppelia Ballet* (L' Aurore), Manuscript full score; later revision (Box 127)
  - Dellinger, Rudolf, 1857-1910
    - Capitän Fracassa*, Printed full score (lithograph) (Box 127)
    - [Don Cäsar]
      - Don Cesar. Hamburg: Aug. Cranz, n.d., Manuscript and printed parts (lithograph) (Box 128-129)
    - Lorraine, Printed full score (lithograph); 2 vols. (Box 130)
  - Donizetti, Gaetano, 1797-1848
    - [Anna Bolena]
      - Anna Bolen, Manuscript full score; 2 vols. (Box 131-132)
    - Betly, Manuscript full score (not the original scoring) (Box 133)
    - Don Pasquale, Manuscript full score (Box 134)
    - Don Pasquale, Manuscript full score; 3 vols. (Box 135)
    - Don Quixote, Manuscript full score (Box 136)
    - L' Elisir d'amore, Manuscript full score; 2 vols.; Act I only (Box 137)
    - Elisir d'amore. Milan: Ricordi, 1916, Printed full score (Box 138)
    - L' Elisir d'amore, Manuscript stage band score (Box 138)
    - L' Elisir d'amore, Manuscript full score; Act II (incomplete) only (Box 138)
    - L' Elisir d'amore, Manuscript full score; Act II only (Box 139)
    - Adina, Manuscript full score (Box 140)
    - La Favorite, Manuscript full score (Box 140)
    - La Fille du regiment, Printed full score; Plate no. S653. (Box 141)
    - Oder die Marie, Manuscript full score; Copy of original French Tochter des Regiments score. (Box 142)
    - Gamma di Vergy. Milan: Ricordi, n.d., Manuscript full score; 2 vols.; Acts I-II only (Box 143-144)
    - Linda di Chamounix, Manuscript full score; 3 vols. (Box 145)
    - Linda di Chamounix, Manuscript full score; Act III only (Box 146)
    - Lucia di Lammermoor, Manuscript full score; 3 vols.; Acts I-III only (Box 146-147)
    - Lucia di Lammermoor, Manuscript full score; 2 vols.; Acts II-III only; [Fragile]. (Box 148)
    - Lucia di Lammermoor, Manuscript full score; 2 vols.; Acts I-II only; [Fragile]. (Box 149)
    - Lucrezia Borgia, Manuscript full score; 4 vols. (Box 150-151)
    - Lucrezia Borgia, Manuscript full score; 3 vols. (Box 152)
    - Lucrezia Borgia, Manuscript full score; Introduzione only (Box 153)
    - Lucrezia Borgia. New York: Guigno [illegible], 1853, Manuscript full score (Box 153)
    - Maria di Rohan, Manuscript and printed parts; Plate nos. B. C. 400, B. C. 440, B. L. 440. (Box 154)
    - Los Martires, Manuscript stage band score (Box 154)
  - Eberwein, [Karl], 1786-1868
    - Lenore, Manuscript piano-vocal score; [Fragile]. (Box 792)
    - Lenore, Manuscript parts (Box 792)
  - Edwards, Julian, 1855-1910
    - [Brian Boru]
      - Brian Boru selection. Cincinnati: John Church Co., 1896, Printed parts; Plate no. 12129-56.; [Fragile]. (Box 155)
    - [Corinna]
      - Corinne, Manuscript full score (Box OV-156)
      - Corinne, Manuscript parts; overture only (Box 157)
      - Corinne (1879), Manuscript full score (incomplete) (Box OV-169)
    - Divertimento in A, Manuscript full score and parts (Box 158-159)
    - [Friend Fritz]
      - Fritz waltzes. Cincinnati: John Church Co., 1894, Printed parts; Plate no. 9889-21-G.; (4 copies). (Box 160)
    - God save the Queen, Manuscript parts (Box 160)
    - The Goddess of truth, Manuscript full score (Box 160)
    - [Jupiter]
      - Potpourri from Jupiter. Cincinnati: John Church Co., n.d., Printed parts; Plate no. 8787-53-G. (Box 161)
    - [King René's daughter]
      - Prelude to King René's daughter. Cincinnati: John Church Co., 1895, Printed full score; manuscript parts; Plate no. 11374-15. (Box 162)
    - [Madeleine]
      - [Madeleine]: Selections from the opera. Cincinnati: John Church Co., 1896, Printed parts; Plate no. 10728-18 3/2. (Box 163)
    - The Redeemer, Manuscript full score (Box 164)
    - Symphonie in A minor, Manuscript full score (Box 164)
  - Engländer, Ludwig, 1853-1914
    - Casino girl, Manuscript full score; 2 vols.; Acts I-II (Box 166)
    - [Strollers]
      - Songs from The Strollers, Manuscript full score; three songs (Box 155)
    - 1776, Manuscript full score; Gavotte only (Box 350)
  - Ernst II, Duke of Saxe-Coburg-Gothe, 1818-1893
    - Diane de Solange, Printed full score (lithograph); [Fragile]. (Box 763)
  - Esser, Heinrich, 1818-1872
    - [Beiden Prinzen]
      - Die Zwei Prinzen, Printed full score (lithograph) (Box 168)
  - Eysler, Edm[und], 1874-1949
    - [Der Lachende Ehemann]
      - Wein-lied, Manuscript parts (Box 792)
  - Fall, Leo[pold], 1873-1925
    - Der Fidele Bauer. Leipzig: C. G. Röder G. m. b. H., n.d., Printed piano-vocal score; Plate nos. 182, 184, and 188.; (Copy 1). (Box 792)
    - Der Fidele Bauer, Printed piano-vocal score; Missing pages 33-62.; (Copy 2). (Box 793)
    - Der Fidele Bauer, Printed piano-vocal score; (Copy 3). (Box 793)
    - Der Fidele Bauer, Folder of duplicate pages (Box 793)
    - Der Fidele Bauer, Printed parts (from manuscript); 1 of 2. (Box 793)
    - Der Fidele Bauer, Printed parts (from manuscript); 2 of 2. (Box 794)
    - Der Fidel Bauer, Manuscript vocal parts (Box 794)
    - Der Fidele Bauer, Printed parts (Box 794)
    - Der Fidele Bauer, Printed libretto (with laid in material) (Box 794)
  - Felix, Hugo
    - Madame Sherry. Berlin: Schlesinger, n.d., Printed piano-vocal score; Plate no. S. 9237.; (2 copies). (Box 796)
    - Madame Sherry, Printed parts (from manuscript) (Box 796)
  - Fetrás, Oscar
    - Frohsinn auf den Bergen. Hamburg: Anton J. Benjamin, n.d., Printed parts; Plate no. A.J.B. 2553. (Box 796)
  - Fischer, Rudolph
    - Primanerliebe. Offenbach a/M: Joh. André, n.d., Printed piano-vocal score; parts; Includes 3 page libretto.; Plate no. 14923.; [Fragile]. (Box 797)
  - Fischer-Bernauer, Karl
    - Lindenwirtin du Junge ... Heidelberg: Karl Hochstein, n.d., Printed libretto (Box 797)
  - Flotow, Friedrich von, 1812-1883
    - Alessandro Stradella. Hamburg: Joh. Aug. Böhme, 1844, Manuscript full score; 3 vols.; Printed title page. (Box 169-170)
    - Martha, Manuscript full score; 2 vols. (Box 171)
    - Martha, Manuscript full score (condensed); supplementary sketches. (Box 172)
    - Marta. Milan: Lucca, n.d., Manuscript full score; 4 vols. (Box 173-174)
    - Marta, Manuscript full score; Act IV only (incomplete) (Box 175)
    - Marta, Manuscript full score (Box 176)
  - Foster, Stephen C(ollins), 1826-1864
    - Old Black Joe, Manuscript parts (Box 176)
    - Home sweet home, Manuscript parts; (2 copies). (Box 176)
    - Old folks at home, Manuscript parts. (Box 176)
  - Francisci, D. M.
    - Prinz Carnevals Brautfahrt, Manuscript parts (Box 797)
    - Prinz Carnevals Brautfahrt, Typed libretto; Typed synopsis.; Miscellaneous material. (Box 797)
  - Fürst, William, 1852-1917
    - Fleur-de-lis*, Manuscript full score (Box 177)
    - The Isle of champagne, Manuscript full score; (3 copies). (Box 178-180)
    - Princess Nicotine, Manuscript full score. (Box 181)
  - Gabriel, [Charles H.], [1856-1932]
    - A Day in the woods, Manuscript full score (Box 182)
  - Gade, Niels W(ilhelm), 1817-1890
    - Die Heilige Nacht. Leipzig: Breitkopf & Härtel, n.d., Printed full score; Plate no. 10492. (Box 182)
  - Gaul, Alfred R(obert), 1837-1913
    - Joan of Arc, Manuscript full score (Box 183)
  - Gebest, Charles J., 1872-1937
    - Beauty shop*, Manuscript full score (Box 183)
  - Gellert, Friedrich
    - Unter der Blühenden Linde. Hamburg: Anton J. Benjamin, n.d., Printed score (from manuscript) (Box 797)
    - Unter der Blühenden Linde. Hamburg: Anton J. Benjamin, n.d., Manuscript parts (Box 797)
    - Unter der Blühenden Linde. Hamburg: Anton J. Benjamin, n.d., Printed libretto (Box 797)
    - Unter der Blühenden Linde. Hamburg: Anton J. Benjamin, n.d., Manuscript parts; loose sheets (Box 797)
  - Genée, Richard, 1823-1895
    - Die Dreizehn. Wien: Gustav Lewy, n.d., Printed full score (lithograph); [Fragile]. (Box 184)
    - The Thirteen Club. Wien: Gustav Lewy, n.d., Printed full score (lithograph) (Box 185)
    - Die Letzten Mohikaner. Wien: Gustav Lewy, n.d., Printed full score (lithograph); (2 copies). (Box 186)
    - Die Letzten Mohikaner, Manuscript fragments; [Fragile]. (Box 186)
    - Der Musikfeind*. Berlin: Bote & Bock, n.d., Printed full score (lithograph) (Box 187)
    - Nanon. Wien: Gustav Lewy, n.d., Manuscript full score; Acts I-II; [Fragile]. (Box 798)
    - Die Piraten. Wien: Gustav Lewy, n.d., Printed full score (lithograph); (2 copies). (Box 188)
    - Die Prinzessin von Kannibalia. Leipzig: C.F.W. Siegel, n.d., Printed piano-vocal full score; Plate no. 3764. (Box 188)
    - Rosina. Hamburg: Aug. Cranz, n.d., Printed full score (lithograph) (Box 189)
    - Der Seekadet*, Printed full score (lithograph); 2 vols. (Box 189)
  - Gilbert, Jean
    - Polnische Wirtschaft. Berlin: W. Mandel & M. Winterfeld, n.d., Printed piano-vocal score (from manuscript); [Fragile]. (Box 799)
    - Polnische Wirtschaft. Berlin: W. Mandel & M. Winterfeld, n.d., Printed parts (from manuscript); [Fragile]. (Box 799)
    - Polnische Wirtschaft. Berlin: W. Mandel & M. Winterfeld, n.d., Printed parts; [Fragile]. (Box 799)
  - Gilmore, Patrick S(arsfield), 1829-1892
    - Columbia, Manuscript parts (Box 190)
  - Giordano, Umberto, 1867-1948
    - Fedora. Milan: Sonzogno, n.d., Printed and manuscript parts; Plate no. 1002. (Box 190)
    - Fedora. Milan: Sonzogno, n.d., Printed and manuscript parts; Plate no. 983. (Box 190)
  - Glück, Christoph Willibald, Ritter von, 1714-1787
    - [Orfeo ed Euridice]
      - Orpheus und Eurydice. Leipzig: Gustav Heinze, 1866, Printed full score; Plate no. G 118 H. (Box 192)
      - Orpheus, Manuscript full score (Box 192)
      - Orpheus. Leipzig: C. F. Peters, n.d., Printed full score; Plate no. 5518. (Box 193)
      - Orpheus. Leipzig: Gustav Heinze, 1866, Printed full score; Plate no. G 118 H. (Box 192)
  - Goetz, Hermann, 1840-1876
    - [Widerspenstigen Zähmung]
      - Wiederspänstigen Zähnung. Leipzig: Fr. Kistner, n.d., Printed full score; Plate no. 4520. (Box 194)
  - Goetze, Walter W.
    - Wenn Männer schwindern...! Berlin: Berliner Musikalien Druckerel G.m.b.H., n.d., Printed piano-vocal score; Plate no. 9830.; (2 copies). (Box 799)
    - Wenn Männer schwindern...! Berlin: Berliner Musikalien Druckerel G.m.b.H.[?], n.d., Duplicate printed parts (from manuscript); Plate no. 9830. (Box 799)
    - Wenn Männer schwindern...! Berlin: Berliner Musikalien Druckerel G.m.b.H.[?], n.d., Printed vocal parts (from manuscript); Plate no. 9830. (Box 799)
  - Gompf, Richard
    - Trutzliesel. Heidelberg: Karl Hochstein, n.d., Printed piano-vocal score; Plate no. H. 2127 H. (Box 804)
    - Trutzliesel. Heidelberg: Karl Hochstein, n.d., Printed libretto; Plate no. H. 2127 H. (Box 804)
    - Trutzliesel. Heidelberg: Karl Hochstein, n.d., Printed parts (from manuscript); Plate no. H. 2127 H. (Box 804)
    - Vergenessenes Heldentum. Heidelberg: Karl Hochstein, n.d., Printed piano-vocal score; Plate no. H. 1397 H.; [Fragile]. (Box 805)
  - Gounod, Charles, 1818-1893
    - Faust, Manuscript full score; Act V Bacchanale. (Box 196)
    - Faust. London: Chappell & Co., 1900, Printed full score; Plate no. 20948.; (2 copies). (Box 196-197)
    - Faust. [Berlin]: Bote & Bock, 1864, Manuscript full score; 2 vols.; Acts I-III (Box 198)
    - Faust. [Berlin]: Bote & Bock, 1864, Manuscript full score; 2 vols.; Acts IV-V (Box 199)
    - Faust. London: Chappell & Co., 1900, Printed full score; Plate no. 20948. (Box 200)
    - Faust. Paris: Choudens, n.d., Printed full score; 2 vols.; Acts I-IV (Box 200)
    - Romeo & Juliette, Manuscript full score; 2 vols. (Box 201-202)
  - Gramichstaedten, Bruno
    - Evelyne. Berlin/München/Wien: Drei Masken=Verlag A. G., n.d., Printed piano-vocal score; Plate no. D.M.V. 3247. (Box 806)
    - Walzerliebe. Leipzig/Wien/New York: W. Karczag, n.d., Printed full score (condensed); Plate no. W.K. 1350. (Box 807)
  - Grüneke, Gothor
    - Ein Böhm in Amerika. Wien: Adolph W. Künast, n.d., Manuscript full score (Box 808)
    - Ein Böhm in Amerika. Wien: Adolph W. Künast, n.d., Manuscript parts (Box 808)
    - Ein Böhm in Amerika. Wien: Adolph W. Künast, n.d., Manuscript vocal parts (Box 808)
    - Ein Böhm in Amerika. Wien: Adolph W. Künast, n.d., Printed libretto score (Box 808)
  - Guiraud, Ernest, 1837-1892
    - Madame Turlupin, Manuscript full score (Box 202)
  - Hahn, Rudolf
    - Er ist Baron oder. Berlin: Edward Bloch, n.d., Printed piano-vocal score (Box 809)
    - Er ist Baron oder. Berlin: Edward Bloch, n.d., Printed libretto (Box 809)
  - Halévy, (Jacques-François-) Fromental, 1799-1862
    - [Juive]
      - The/Die Jüdin Jewess*, Manuscript full score (Box 203)
    - [Mousquetaires de la reine]
      - Maid of Honor (Les Mousquetaires de la reine), Manuscript full score (Box 204)
  - Handel, George Frideric, 1685-1759
    - Acis and Galatea. London: Goulding, d'Almaine, Potter & Co., n.d., Printed full score.; Plate nos. 28-30. (Box 205)
    - Alexander's feast. London: Novello, n.d., Printed parts; Accompaniment by W.A. Mozart. (Box 205)
    - Alexanders Fest oder die Gewalt. Leipzig: C. F. der Musik Peters, n.d., Printed full score; Accompaniment by W.A. Mozart.; Plate nos. 1049 & 1089. (Box 210)
    - Israel in Egypt, Printed full score; Plate nos. 92-98. (Box 206)
    - Redemption. London: Rt. Birchall, n.d., Printed full score; Arranged by Samuel Arnold. (Box 208)
    - Samson. London: Novello, Ewer & Co., n.d., Printed parts; Additional accompaniment by E. Prout.; Plate no. 6008. (Box 209)
    - Samson, Manuscript part (bass) of no. 14 only (Box 209)
  - Hanson, Howard
    - Symphony No. 11 "Romantic". Boston: C. C. Birchard and Company, n.d., Printed full score (Box 810)
  - Harbort, Gottfried, 1768-1837
    - Das Hirten Maedchen, Oder die Amors Triumph, Manuscript full score; Act I only (Box 211)
  - Harty, (Herbert) Hamilton, Sir, 1879-1941
    - "Homeward". London: Novello & Co., Ltd., 1911, Printed piano-vocal score; Plate no. 13376. (Box 14)
  - Hauptner, Thuiskon, 1821-1889
    - Coeur Bube, Manuscript full score (Box 211)
    - Singvögelchen. Berlin: Eduard Bloch, n.d., Printed piano-vocal score (Box 811)
    - Singvögelchen, Manuscript parts; Script parts.; Typed synopsis. (Box 811)
  - Haydn, (Franz) Joseph, 1732-1809
    - Jahreszeiten. Leipzig: C. F. Peters, n.d., Printed full score; Plate no. 5655. (Box 212)
    - Mass no. 2. London: Novello, n.d., Printed and manuscript parts (Box 212)
    - Mass no. 3. London: Novello, n.d., Printed and manuscript parts (Box 212)
    - [Schöpfung]
      - The Creation. London: Novello, 1859, Printed full score (Box 213)
  - Heartz, Harry Lawson, 1873-?
    - Miss Simplicity*, Manuscript full score (Box 214)
    - Miss Simplicity*, Manuscript parts; Nos 21, 22, Act II Finale only (Box 214)
  - Hellmesberger, Joseph, 1828-1893
    - Graf von Gleichen, Manuscript full score; [Fragile]. (Box 215)
    - Das Orakel. Wien: Gustav Lewy, n.d., Printed full score (lithograph) (Box 215)
    - Rikiki. Wien: Gustav Lewy, n.d., Printed full score (lithograph); [Fragile]. (Box 216)
    - Das Veilchenmädel. Wien: Josef Eberle, n.d., Printed piano-vocal score; Plate no. J.E. 869. (Box 812)
  - Henschel, (Isidor) George, Sir, 1850-1934
    - Hamlet. London: Novello, Ewer & Co., 1892, Printed full score; Plate no. 9318. (Box 216)
  - Hense, Paul
    - Hans Lange. Berlin: Wilhelm Herb, 1876, Printed libretto (Box 813)
  - Herbert, Victor, 1859-1924
    - Amerikanische Fantasie/American fantasy. [Hamburg]: Schuberth & Co., 1898, Manuscript and printed parts (some printed from manuscript); Plate no. 2107. (Box 217)
    - The Duchess, Manuscript full score, parts and piano-vocal score; Life is a riddle; Manuscript parts for What's the use; Introductory chorus (Box 222)
    - The Duchess, Manuscript parts (Box 223-225)
    - Girl in the spotlight, Manuscript parts for Everything has stung me but a bee; A Savage I remain (Box 218)
    - The Idol's eye, Manuscript full score; parts (for miscellaneous numbers) (Box 219)
    - Lady of the slipper, Manuscript parts for The voice of the waltz, Ballet suite, Overture, Fairy tales, Schottische & Essence, Encore to stop dance; Act II; manuscript military band parts for Overture (Box 220-221)
    - Legende for violoncelle, Manuscript full score (Box 786)
    - The Madcap duchess, Manuscript parts (Box 226-227)
    - Natoma, Manuscript full score; Acts I & III; miscellaneous excerpts (Box 228)
    - Natoma, Piano-vocal score (Box 229)
    - Natoma, Manuscript full score; Includes: Act I, rehearsal 1-34 (original score); Act I, rehearsal 35-77 (original score); Act I, scene 1, pages 21-27; Act I, scene 7; Act II, No. 6, Vaqueros song; Act II, They come; Around thy rod (includes Peralta's blessing not in published score); Act III, Prelude (original score); miscellaneous score pages [cuts]. (Box 230)
    - Natoma, Manuscript full score; Includes: Act I, scene 1, rehearsal 1-34 (duplicate score); Act I, Nos. 5A & 5B (original score); Act II, Prelude, scene 1 (original score); Act II, No. 6, Vaqueros song (original score); Act II, Habañera; Act II, No. 7, Festival procession (original score); Act II, No. 8, Spring song. (Box 231)
    - Natoma, Manuscript parts: Habañera; 3 printed programs. (Box 232)
    - Natoma, Manuscript full score; parts; Excerpts.; Miscellaneous sketches. (Box 233)
    - Natoma, Manuscript full score; parts; Includes: Dagger dance; Vaquero's song; Pañuelo Act I, No. 6. (Box 234)
    - Natoma, Manuscript parts; old parts [cuts?] (Box 234A)
    - Natoma, Manuscript full score; Includes: Act I, No. 3; Act I, No. 4; Act I, rehearsal 224-241; Act II, Prelude (in pencil); Act II, No. 2; Act II, No. 9; Act II, No. 11; Miscellaneous, p. 17-25, scene 2, scene 6. (Box 235)
    - Natoma, Manuscript parts; Act I; Act I, scene 5 Drinking chorus (Box 764)
    - Natoma, Manuscript parts; Act II (miscellaneous); Act III Beware of the hawk (Box 765)
    - Natoma, Manuscript piano-vocal score; parts; Act 1, miscellaneous; Act I, Paul's address; Act II, Prelude, Nos. 1, 6-8; unidentified parts and score. (Box 784)
    - Natoma, Manuscript parts; Act II, Pañuelo; Spring song; No. 7 Festival procession; Act I, Love duet. (Box 785)
    - Natoma, Manuscript full score; Act I, scene 5A (duplicate score); Act II, No. 4 (original score); Act II, No. 5 (original score); manuscript parts and stageband score; manuscript guitar score; Act I, scene 2. (Box 787)
    - Qui Madame, Manuscript parts; selections only (Box 786)
    - Peg Woffington, Manuscript parts (Box 236-237)
    - The Serenade, Manuscript full score; [Fragile]. (Box 238)
    - Singing girl*, Manuscript full score; piano-vocal score (Box 238A)
    - Some colonel, Manuscript parts (Box 238B-238C)
    - Under the red robe, Manuscript parts (Box 239)
    - Viceroy, Manuscript full score; parts (Box 240)
  - Hérold, Ferdinand, 1791-1833
    - Zampa, Printed parts; Plate no. J.M. 539. (Box 241-242)
    - Zampa, Manuscript full score; printed parts; Plate no. J.M. 539. (Box 242)
  - Hervé (Rogner, Florimond), 1825-1892
    - Chilpéric*, Manuscript parts (Box 243)
    - Le Petit Faust, Manuscript full score (Box 244)
    - Le Petit Faust, Manuscript parts; [Fragile]. (Box 245)
  - Hiller, F(erdinand von), 1811-1885
    - Israel's Siegesgesang. Leipzig: F. E. C. Leuckart, n.d., Printed full score (lithograph) (Box 246)
  - Hirsch, Louis A(chille), 1887-1924
    - Going up, Manuscript full score; Includes one number by Irving Berlin.; [Fragile]. (Box 246)
    - Home town girl, Manuscript full score; Nurse number only (Box 247)
  - Hofmann, Heinrich, 1842-1902
    - Aschenbrödel. Berlin: Hermann Erler, n.d., Printed full score; Plate no. 500. (Box 247)
  - Hollaender, Victor, 1866-1940
    - [Yvette]
      - Ivette, Manuscript full score (Box 248)
  - Horn, August, 1825-1893
    - Die Nachbarn. Leipzig: Fr. Kistner, n.d., Printed full score (lithograph); Plate nos. 4314 & 4364. (Box 248)
  - Hoschna, Karl, 1877-1911
    - Across the continent, Manuscript full score (Box 249)
    - Back again, Manuscript full score (Box 360)
    - Bright eyes, Manuscript full score (Box 249)
    - Doctor De Luxe*, Manuscript full score; Arranged by Hans S. Linné. (Box 249)
    - The Girl of my dreams, Manuscript full score (Box 250)
    - Katy did, Manuscript full score; Arranged by Hans S. Linné. (Box 250)
    - Prince Humbug, Manuscript full score (Box 251)
    - Three twins, Manuscript full score (Box 251)
  - Hummel, Johann Nepomuk, 1778-1837
    - Misse mit Deutschen Text, Manuscript full score (Box 251)
  - Humperdinck, Engelbert
    - Hänsel und Gretel. New York: F. Rullman, n.d., Printed libretto (Box 814)
    - Königskinder. Leipzig: Max Brockhaus, n.d., Printed piano-vocal score; Plate no. M. B. 280 I. (Box 815)
  - Impekoven, Loni und Mathern, Carl
    - Otto der Treue. Berlin: Wilmersdorf, n.d., Printed libretto (Box 816)
  - Isouard, Nicolo, 1775-1818
    - [Cendrillon]
      - Aschenbrödel, Manuscript full score; 2 vols. (Box 253)
  - Jarno, Georg
    - Die Förster-Christel. Berlin: Harmonie G. m. b. H., n.d., Printed piano-vocal score; Plate no. ch. 198. (Box 817)
    - Die Förster-Christel, Printed piano-vocal score (miscellaneous)(2 folders) (Box 817)
    - Die Förster-Christel, Printed parts (from manuscript)(2 folders) (Box 817)
    - Die Förster-Christel, Printed and manuscript vocal parts; miscellaneous (Box 817)
  - Jensen, Adolf, 1837-1879
    - Gesang der Nonnen. Hamburg: Fritz Schuberth, n.d., Printed full score; Plate no. 742. (Box 254)
  - Jessel, Leon
    - Postmeisterin. Berlin: Richard Birnbach, n.d., Printed piano-vocal score; Plate no. D.C. 222. (Box 818)
    - Postmeisterin, Printed parts (from manuscript) (Box 818)
  - Jones, Sidney, 1861-1946
    - San toy, Manuscript full score (Box 253)
  - Kalliwoda, Johann Wenzeslaus, 1800-1866
    - Messe in A dur. Mainz: Schott, n.d., Printed full score (Box 262)
  - Kálmán, Emmerich, 1882-1953
    - Der Zigeunerprimas. Leipzig: Josef Weinberger, 1912, Printed parts (lithograph) (Box 254)
  - Kelley, Edgar Stillman, 1857-1944
    - Ben Hur, Manuscript full score (Box 254)
  - Kerker, Gustave, 1857-1923
    - Burning to sing, Manuscript full score (Box 255)
    - Kismet, Manuscript full score (Box 255)
    - The Tourists, Manuscript full score; parts: That's the time Oh, Mr. Sun only (Box 255)
  - Klein, Manuel, 1876-1919
    - It's up to you, Manuscript full score; Everytime I see you (Box 788)
    - Mr. Pickwick, Manuscript full score; parts; piano-vocal score (Box 256)
    - Mr. Pickwick. New York: M. Witmark & Sons, 1903, Printed piano-vocal score; Kisses and cakes plate no. a4936.; For love is king plate nos. 5223-5226. (Box 256)
  - Klerr, Johann Baptist, 1830-1875
    - Das War ich, oder die böse Nachtbarin, Manuscript full score; (2 copies). (Box 257)
  - Koller, August
    - Bub oder Mädel oderIch weiss etwas!, Typed libretto (Box 819)
  - Konradin, Karl Ferdinand, 1833-1884
    - Liebchen auf dem Dache, Manuscript full score (Box 258)
  - Konti, Josef, 1852-1905
    - Die Taugenichts*, Manuscript full score (Box 258)
  - Kral, Johann Nepomuk, 1839-1896
    - Gestort*, Manuscript full score (Box 259)
  - Kremser, Edward, 1838-1914